eztocreate.com 2009-04-25

# Highlights of Privacy Policy

**HIGHLIGHTS OF PRIVACY POLICY  
EFFECTIVE: JANUARY 5, 2007**

We want you to be informed of our privacy practices. The following applies to our websites, and products, and covers how we collect and use the information we receive. This is only a summary, for more information, please read our complete Privacy Policy.

**Information We Collect**     Additional details

  * We collect information you choose to submit, for example, when you download one of our products, subscribe to our online services, or participate in a survey or contest.
  * We may obtain additional information about you, such as updated address, demographic or lifestyle information, from other sources.
  * We use common Internet technologies, such as cookies, on our Web sites and in our e-mails.

**Uses of information**     Additional details

  * We use the information you submit to provide our services including the presentation of personalized content.
  * We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by us and our partners.
  * We may share information about you with vendors we have hired to provide services on our behalf.
  * We may share information about you with our partners and companies that provide online content, if those companies host that content.
  * We will share your e-mail address with other companies, if you consent.
  * We may share your name and postal address with our subsidiaries and selected other companies for mail offers of their products and services, if you consent.

**Your Choices**     Additional details

  * You may unsubscribe from our e-mail list.
  * You may direct us not to share your e-mail with other companies for offers of their products and services. You may also turn off cookies in your browser.

**Important information**

  * For information and tips on children’s online privacy visit [www.ftc.gov/privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy) and [www.OnGuardOnline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/)
  * Any personal information you provide will be maintained in the United States
  * We encourage you to read our full Privacy Policy

**How to contact us**  
Questions about our Privacy policy or about Freeze’s handling of your information may be sent via e-mail to: either by accessing [http://support.freeze.com](http://support.freeze.com/) or by sending a message to [privacy@support.w3i.com](mailto:privacy@support.w3i.com). If you would prefer to write to us please send your correspondence to:

W3i, LLC  
Attention: Customer Care – Privacy Policy Issues  
1900 Medical Arts Ave. S. Ste. 200  
Sartell, MN 56377
